my church friend at church, she said
that um she couldn't believe that I put
a harness on my kids and I said, "Well,
I just want him to live.
I'm so excited to be here. I FLEW IN
FROM OHIO where I live on a farm. So, uh
this is a big night out for me.
This is like Las Vegas.
This is like Disneyland.
I get to talk to people and not animals.
And guess what else? It's my birthday.
>> And I'm not afraid to say my age. I am
85 years old.
>> I figure if you're going to lie, you
need to lie up.
Cuz I don't want to say I'm 40 and you
say, "Oh,
holy mackerel.
What happened to that poor lady? She
looks like she was hit by a car and left
by the side of the road for dead. But if
I say I'm 85, you'll say I want what
she's got. Right.
As we get older, right, ladies, natural
beauty takes time.
So, I started doing my makeup on Monday
and I finished about an hour ago.
My sister says, "Don't worry about your
lines on your face, Leslie." She said,
"We should embrace every line on our
face." She says she has earned every
line on her face. And I thought to
myself, I think she got ripped off
cuz mine came for free.
I uh since we're friends and it's my
birthday, I will admit I have had a
little plastic surgery.
My friends think I've had too much since
I used to be a tall black man.
I wished I was making that up.
And this is my hair. I have naturally
curly hair. I am blessed with this hair
that no matter how miserable I go to bed
at night, MY HAIR WAKES UP HAPPY.
GOOD MORNING, LESIE.
And I uh I tried to look my best for you
all this evening. Thank you. Thank you.
And I always when I get all dressed up,
I always say to my husband, I say, "How
do I look?" And he says, "You look
fine."
Fine. Not what I want to hear. Right,
ladies?
What I want to hear is fabulous,
beautiful, thin.
Is this too much to ask?
WOULDN'T IT BE GREAT IF your man was
like uh you could put a little computer
chip into his neck and every time you
touch it, he'd say all the things you
always wanted to hear?
You touch it and he'd say, "That diamond
is much too small."
You touch it and he'd say,
>> "I have gas. I'm going into the next
room."
You touch it and you'd say, "I'm lost.
Let's ask for directions.
Of
>> course, my husband would think it would
be better if he could put a computer
chip into my neck. You would touch it
and I'd say nothing
because he he thinks I talk too much.
He actually it was a little rude what he
told me recently. He said my voice was
irritating.
Sometimes he says to me, "Could you
could you stop talking? Would you hush
up? Could you could you stop? Could you
just could you hush up? WOULD YOU JUST
SHUT UP?" And I just keep talking.
And my husband uh he says my voice uh
doesn't come in handy all the time, but
when we lived in Hollywood, I lived in
Los Angeles, I auditioned for the
original phone voice of the iPhone,
Siri,
and they told me if I had gotten the
part, they would have renamed her Sorry.
SO NOW I ABOUT ACTUALLY ABOUT um 10
years ago my husband said we were going
to move our family from Hollywood and we
were going to live in his
hundredyear-old family farm. It was
vacant for over a hundred years and we
were going to raise our children in
God's country. And I was thinking to
myself, I'll have the adventure. I'm a
comedian, right? I was thinking Gone
with the Wind,
Field of Dreams. You know, babe, a
Disney's babe. People working in the
field, mama cooking biscuits and gravy
in the kitchen. Come and get it. We
rolled into his hundred-year-old family
farm. There were animals on the roof, a
couch on the front porch, weeds
everywhere. It looked like an episode of
Duck Dynasty.
And I started to cry and tears welled up
in my face. And my husband said, "What
is wrong?" And I said, "Well, where are
the people?" He said, "You are the
people."
He said, "BUT YOU CAN DO WHATEVER YOU
WANT TO TO THIS PLACE." And I said, "Can
we burn it?"
My first birthday on the farm.
Absolutely. True story. My husband gave
me six chickens.
Yes, he is a member of the bird family.
Cheap, cheap, cheap, cheap.
Six. that that you'll laugh at later on.
Six chickens and soon we had 286
chickens. He said, "Let's eat the
chickens." I said, "Eat the neighbors."
He said, "Let's eat the eggs." I said,
"Eat the neighbors, children." I said,
"You go to the grocery STORE AND GET
SOME OF THOSE HOMELESS EGGS. Those I
could eat."
They have names and it's very Any farmer
people out there? Anybody lived on a
farm? by applause.
Couple people. How about flown over a
farm? How about that one?
>> Yes. One morning, absolutely true story,
my husband woke me up and he said,
"Let's go pull a calf." I said, "You
know, I hate aerobics."
Cuz I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT THAT MEANT. SO,
AS I I GOT ALL DRESSED up every time I
went anywhere on the farm. So, I put on
my $75 Reebok on and my Under Armour
outfit and I go walking out to our field
thinking I might meet somebody. Somebody
might talk to me. And as I got closer to
our prize cow, there was a prized cow
and she was hunched over really ugly and
there was a thing coming out the back
part, you know, and the and and and the
cow was mooing really tragic. It was
m
and my husband said the cow will die if
we don't help her. So I ran to the front
of the cow and I went.
HE SAID DO SOMETHING. I SAID YOU'RE
HAVING MY BABY.
He said now when the cow goes down I
want you to sit on her head.
Isn't that rude and insensitive?
Can you imagine the doctor telling your
husband, "Go sit on her head."
Of course, some of you might like it out
there. How about that one? But he was
great. He's fearless. And he's a real
man. He got in the back of that cow.
True story. And he took those little
bitty hoofs and he pulled and he pulled
and he pulled and it came out
and everything else came with it. I
said, "Put that stuff back in. and it
looks important.
That's been like my life on the farm.
And I I waited a long time to find my
husband. I had my career before I had my
husband. And I had searched this whole
world to find that one special man who
could say those three special words, "I
have money."
And I knew he loved me cuz he asked me
what my ring size was. And I told him
anything over two carats would be fine.
Funny when you live on a farm in the
middle of the tundra, you know, you the
the three words change to I want heat
because it's really really cold out
there. But I learned a lot about my
husband. I remember in the beginning,
how many of y'all are married out there
by applause? Where are the married
people?
We're the single people.
Not quite as happy as those married
people,
but having a husband, it's just musical
to say the word husband, isn't it? Say
it with me. Husband.
Husband. Got to get your lip going up to
your nostril.
Just saying the word. I I remember the
first year we were married, having a
husband. I went to buy him a Valentine
card. The girl said, "Do you want a
sweetheart or a honey card?" I said, "I
want a husband card."
People ask me where do you go at night?
I say I'm going to be with my husband.
Visa called and said I'm over my limit.
I said speak to my husband.
Men used TO FLIRT WITH ME. I'D SAY I
have a husband which is better than what
I used to say. I have a disease.
And is it just my husband or do ALL MEN
HAVE TO SAVE EVERY t-shirt from the last
25 years?
Yeah, ON THIS GROSS BLACK RIPPED UP
THING. I SAID, "THROW THAT ON." NO, IT'S
THE FIRST TIME I CHANGED MY OIL IN my 77
Chevrolet.
I mean, when you throw a t-shirt out
that says the Partridge Family World
Tour.
It's just my husband. And And is it just
my husband or do all men have to
separate their laundry like this?
Clean.
Dirty.
What do you do when they do this one?
I'm thinking it's dirty.
He says it's good for one more wear.
And is it just my husband? I just asked
him to to to make the bed. It's not that
hard. It's a pillow sham. It's it's a
comforter. It's not hard to make a bed.
Uh, now he's informed me though now that
he can make the bed while he is in the
bed.
What he does is he lies really flat. He
pulls the comforter over his head and
then he kind of scooshes out the side
and changing the sheets. Can your
husband change the sheets? It's not that
difficult. I went on a tour for two
weeks. I came back. He put new sheets on
top of the old sheets.
to get into bed. I had to use a
stepladder
and he hates to wash the clothes, but he
loves to wash the car. Is it just my
husband? So, you know what I do? I am
very smart. I put all of his dirty
underwear in the rag pile by the car.
HE'S SCRUBBING AWAY AT THAT CAR AND THAT
UNDERWEAR IS SPOTLESS.
BUT it's uh really hard to get the skin
marks out of the car.
I must have crossed the line there.
And I AM A MOTHER. ANYBODY HAVE KIDS OUT
THERE? I am a mom.
I'm an old mom. I had my children later
in life. And as it suffers to say, I
prayed and prayed. I wanted a a little
girl. I just wanted a little girl
because I would know what to teach her.
Buy more clothes. You're a princess.
But you change when you have a son,
right, ladies? You think if a girl did
that to my son, I'd think that
manipulating
girl,
what kind of A MOTHER DOES SHE HAVE? And
of course, the doctor told me that my
eggs were too old.
They told me my eggs were scrambled.
Actually,
he told me that my eggs had little crows
feet and a little walker and those
little fishies. Wait.
Yes. He told me I COULDN'T HAVE ANY
CHILDREN, BUT GOD had a different plan
in mind.
Thank you. And I am the mother of a
beautiful I had a little boy. I had a
well he was he was 10 and a half pounds.
>> Instead of a birth certificate they gave
him a driver's license. People would ask
me what did I crave? I said a surrogate
mother.
My body felt LIKE A LITTLE VOLKSWAGEN IN
THE CIRCUS. YOU KNOW REMEMBER THE CIRCUS
WHERE the clowns all just kept coming
out?
That's a visual coming out.
And we we argued about naming uh my
sweet precious first angel. We uh he the
husband wanted to name my son Moses.
Moses Joseph so we could nickname him
Mojo.
And then I THOUGHT I COULDN'T HAVE
ANOTHER CHILD, BUT GOD HAD another idea
in mind. So, we had our second one and
we called him oops
and then I got spayed
cuz I'm on the farm, right? I thought
that boys WOULD JUST, YOU KNOW, BOYS ARE
JUST SO ACTIVE. I just didn't know about
boys. I didn't know that they just
didn't sit still. You know, I had been a
beauty queen. So, I I would walk normal.
I would just walk like a girl. I would
walk lovely, you know, walk lovely. And
I take my two kids to the mall and I'm
walking walking AND WALKING. WHERE ARE
YOU?
They just are so they were just so
active. In fact, I put I had to put a
harness on the two boys and the church
my church friend at church, she said
that um she couldn't believe that I put
a harness on my kids. And I said, "Well,
I just want him to live."
I didn't KNOW THAT THE BOYS WOULDN'T
JUST LOVE each other automatically.
I didn't know I HAD TO HYPNOTIZE THE BIG
ONE INTO LOVING THE LITTLE ONE. We love
our brother.
We do not hurt our brother. We do not
put a pillow over our brother's head.
And all they could say back to me is,
"Red rum. Red rum. Red rum."
And then of course they were so active.
I put them in front of the TV and Barney
was playing back then. Remember Barney?
And you know, I always felt like a bad
mother cuz Barney would say to the kids,
"Do you want a piece of candy or an
apple?" And the kid would say, "I want
an apple." Not a normal human child. You
know, they were going to GROW UP IN SOME
REPRESSED BANK ROBBER SINGING, "I HATE
YOU. You hate me. I'm in a dysfunctional
family with a great big smack and a kick
from you to me. Now I'm seeking therapy.
I taught my babies my own little nursery
rhyme. It went like this. And the seat
goes down, down, down. And we wipe the
rim rim rim. Cuz late at night night,
mommy won't fall in in.
So, thank you. But I I decided, you
know, MY CHILDREN WERE JUST SO ACTIVE
AND I HAD THIS career that I just loved
and I was living in the middle of
nowhere and and I decided I was going to
stay at home with my children because no
one else would watch them.
They were just so hard and I and I just
said I God gave me these kids and I am
going to do my best. I'm going to be you
stay at home moms are the heroes of the
universe.
>> You are I didn't know it was THAT TOUGH.
I THOUGHT IT'D BE EASY. You know, what
could it be? Just watch two kids at
home. The first year I did okay. I um I
was depressed a bit and I twitched a
bit. I started to twitch just a bit, but
I made it through the first year. And
then the second year I started to, you
know, I started to twitch and I started
to yell a bit. I was yelling at the
toddler, "GET OFF THE COUNTER." AND THE
TODDLER WOULD get all scared and I ran
into the bathroom cuz I thought, "What
if I were to die right then? That would
be the last face that he would see of
his mom." I didn't want to be that kind
of a mother. So, so I tried to change
and I on the second year and I made it
through. I did make it through the
second year and on the third year now I
wanted to pour myself a drink at 5:00,
but then Dr. Oz came on at 2. So, I
thought if I poured it at 2, I'd be a
bad mother. But if I poured it at five,
I just need a 12step program.
But on the third year, I started to
pray. I decided to go back to church.
And I started to pray. And I said,
"Lord, could you help me?" And then on
the third year, no answer.
And on the fourth year, now I'm praying
some more. I'm going to church every
Wednesday. I'm going Saturday. I'm going
there there are prayer chains around
every denomination in my in my neighbor
in my town. And there was Leslie needs
some help. Those kids, those kids are
wacky. She needs some help.
And no answer on the fourth year. And on
the fifth year,
I kept I kept it up. And on the fifth
year, you think that a miracle can't
happen in your life. And a miracle
happened.
The school bus came to my house.
and an angel of the Lord WAS DRIVING
and he SAID TO ME, "I'M GOING TO PICK
YOUR SON UP AT 7 IN THE MORNING AND I'M
GOING TO DROP HIM OFF AT 4 IN THE
AFTERNOON." I SAID, "OH, THANK YOU,
LORD."
I SAID, "HOW MUCH IS THIS GOING TO
COST?" AND HE SAID, "It's free."
I said, "Well, can you COME ON SATURDAY
AND SUNDAY, TOO?"
The truth is, I miss the kids. I waited
for them to leave, and now they're all
grown up, and now I miss them so
terribly. They're at They're at Ohio
State. They're in college. They're at
one is just graduated. And I And I I My
son says, "Mom, it's not Ohio State.
It's the Ohio State. It's the Ohio
State." I said, "Quit Quit bugging me or
else I'm not going to send you the rent.
And then the big boy, you know, he he
got in a veterary medicine school. I was
so proud of him. And then he called me
up and he said that he he didn't he
didn't want to go. He wanted to be play
his guitar in Nashville.
And as I hunched over crying for the
next year,
I realized that my prayer changed from I
wanted my son to be a doctor to now I
want my son to marry a doctor.
AND THEN MY MY MY BABY WAS DOING THE
FOOT. HE LIKED THE football stuff. Do
you like football out here in Utah?
>> Because you know I'M IN SHOW BUSINESS.
WHAT DO I KNOW ABOUT FOOTBALL? AND IN
OHIO, you know, football is king. It's
King. And my kid said to me, he wanted
to play football. And I didn't I But you
you tried. You jump in there cuz you're
a good mom, right? So I asked him cuz I
wanted to help him. Where's your
costume?
When is the rehearsal? What part are you
playing? He said, "Mom, it's a uniform.
It's a practice. And I'm a tight end."
I said, "Well, wear clean underwear is
all I got to say."
CUZ I DIDN'T KNOW ABOUT THIS FOOTBALL
THING. SO THEN I tried harder and I
called up the director
and I asked HIM, "WHAT MUST MY KID DO TO
BE successful at this football thing?"
And he said, "He'll need a cup."
I said, "6 12 or 18 ounces."
Cuz I didn't know about this football
thing. AND THEN THE DIRECTOR told me
that my kid would need a mouth guard.
You know what that is? that protects his
teeth. I just put $4,000 worth of braces
on my kid's head. And the mission of the
other big lug is to knock it out of his
head. I'M GONNA BE BUYING HIM DENTURES
WHILE AT THE SAME TIME PAYING OFF HIS
BRACES. I am driving a 1996 Ford Escort
so my kid could have a beautiful smile.
I am driving my kid smile. And the
director said he's needs a mouth guard.
I didn't enjoy this. And then he told me
that this football thing is not inside.
It's outside. And it's November and
October and it's snowing and it's
sleeping and all those football moms are
in. THEY'RE IN THE BLEACHERS. THEY'RE
GOING, "GO D." THEY'RE SO HAPPY. GO D.
GO D. And I'm thinking, COULD YOU GET to
the end of the alphabet?
I'm cold. About an hour passes.
Everybody starts to leave. Intermission.
As I start to leave, I notice on the on
the performance space out there, I
notice there's like dancing girls and
they have costumes on and there's music.
AND I YELLED TO THE PEOPLE LEAVING,
"COME BACK. COME BACK. YOU'RE GOING TO
MISS THE SHOW." AND I COULDN'T HELP
MYSELF. I just stood up on the bleachers
and I started to sing
a little louder, please.
Don't let them see. Don't let them
guess. His mom's in the bleachers. She's
a mess. It's violent this football
thing.
And so I scream,
"Let him live. Let him live."
But the coach says go.
He's on defense real low. The football
gets a snap.
He runs around this kid to sack the
quarterback.
Another kid, 300 lb, jumps on his back.
Six other kids pile on. He's at the
bottom of the stair.
LET HIM GO. LET him go. Can't you see?
He's just my kid. Let him go. Let him
go. He's got braces in his head.
Can't you see what this is costing me?
And the coach says, "Go."
My son said, "Mom, if you go to the
game, please don't talk to anyone."
THANK YOU SO MUCH. HEY,
HEY, HEY.